whyisthismansmiling.com 2010-02-09

# Why is this Man Smiling? | The Adventures of Smiley Raj | Privacy-Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

This site is operated on behalf of whyisthismansmiling.com. whyisthismansmiling.com has developed certain privacy practices that relate to information collected or used in connection with this site as described below. This policy does not apply to information collected by whyisthismansmiling.com in other forums, including over the phone, offline, through emails that you voluntarily send to us, or to information collected on whyisthismansmiling.com websites on which this policy does not apply. whyisthismansmiling.com strives to comply with all applicable laws, rules and regulations. We use appropriate industry standard means, including technical safeguards, to protect any sensitive information that might be submitted on this site.

whyisthismansmiling.com does not require visitors to submit personal information to visit our web sites; however, we do require visitors to submit personal information to register for specific promotions or participate in certain online programs, surveys, newsletters or other transactions or activities. On a particular whyisthismansmiling.com registration page, we may request the visitor’s date of birth, gender, email address, telephone number, and/or other contact and demographic information. whyisthismansmiling.com may collect non-personal information from online visitors, such as the visitor’s browser type, operating system and domain name. 

The non-personal information we collect enables us to track the total number of visitors to each of our sites in an aggregate form, and is used by whyisthismansmiling.com to improve and update our sites, products and services. Aggregate (non-personal) information may be shared with third parties in our discretion. whyisthismansmiling.com reserves the right to limit participation in particular programs or promotions to visitors 18 years of age or older, and does not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years of age.

whyisthismansmiling.com uses information submitted by visitors as described at the time information is collected, and to keep track of visitors' participation in our promotions and programs, to respond to comments or questions, to notify a visitor if he or she is the potential winner of a promotion, to send special messages regarding our sites, products, programs or promotions, to provide visitors with access to special areas or features of our site(s),  and for internal and business purposes. 

whyisthismansmiling.com does not share personal information about visitors to third parties. During certain joint promotions or in other limited circumstances, visitors may have the option to submit personal information to and receive future communications from our joint promotion partner. If you decide to give your contact information to our joint promotion partner, whyisthismansmiling.com is not responsible for the third party content or the use of information by such third parties. whyisthismansmiling.com may disclose personal information to comply with applicable law or process, if whyisthismansmiling.com believes it is necessary to cooperate with government or other enforcement officials, or to protect our company or the safety of our site visitors. We may hire trusted companies to help us with our websites, programs and promotions, and those companies may have limited access to personal information for the sole purpose of performing their services, subject to confidentiality obligations.

This Privacy Policy may be modified by whyisthismansmiling.com at any time by updating this posting. You are encouraged to check back periodically to review the Privacy Policy.

Share
